schoola.com 2017-08-06

# Privacy Policy | Schoola

## Schoola™ : Privacy Policy

Last Updated: July 14, 2015

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We (Schoola, Inc.) are providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you use the Schoola™ website (including any mobile or other version of that site that we may offer) or the services we provide through Schoola.com (all of the foregoing, our “Website”). This Privacy Policy applies only to our Website and doesn’t apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Website. 

## How do we collect and use information?

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Website, to administer your use of the Website (including your Schoola account if you have one), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Website. 

_Account and Transaction Information._ When you create an account, make a purchase, or engage in other similar transactions on our Website, we’ll request and collect certain information that can be used to identify you, such as your name, email address, credit card number, postal address and phone number (“PII”). We may also collect certain information that is not PII because it cannot be used by itself to identify you, such as your gender, date of birth and zip code. 

_Information Collected Using Cookies._ We collect certain information through the use of “cookies,” which are small text files that are saved by your browser when you access our Website. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to identify that you’ve logged in to the Website and to tell us how and when you interact with our Website. We may also use cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Website and to customize and improve our Website. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted when you log off from the Website and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept cookies, you may not be able to use all portions or features of the Website. Some third-party services providers that we engage (including third-party advertisers) may also place their own cookies on your browser. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not include use of cookies by such third parties. 

_Information Related to Use of the Website._ Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Website (we refer to this information as “Log Data”). Log Data may include information such as a user’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a user was on before accessing our Website, the pages or features of our Website that a user visited and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Website that a user clicked on and other statistics. We use this information to administer the Website and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance the Website by expanding its features and functionality and tailoring them to our users’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s IP address to fight spam, malware and identity theft, and to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Website is used. 

_Location Information._ In some cases we collect and store information about where you are located, such as by converting your IP address into a rough geolocation. We may use location information to improve and personalize our Website for you. 

_Web Beacons._ Our Website and our related e-mail correspondence may contain “web beacons.” Web beacons allow us to count users that have visited a web page or opened an email that contains a web beacon and collect other types of aggregate information. Using this information, we are able to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Website. This allows us to tailor our Website to the interests of our visitors. Some of the web beacons that are in place on our Website are used only by Schoola, and other web beacons are from our vendors and advertisers who use this data to assist us in analyzing how our users use the Website. In addition, we may have agreements with various affiliate networks that promote the Website on their affiliate websites. These affiliate advertisers may use web beacons in their advertisements to track users who click through from the affiliate website to the Website. 

_Email and Newsletters._ We may send you service-related announcements and emails from time to time. Where these communications are related to the administration of your account or your use of the Website, you may not be able to opt out (without deactivating your account). We may also use your information to send you e-newsletters, updates and communications about Schoola. You may opt-out of receiving these messages as described at the bottom of each communication. 

_Demographic and Remarketing._ We may use information provided via analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to analyze the demographic information (including age, gender and interests) of users to inform and optimize content and advertising. This includes ads we serve through other websites based on your activities on our website via Google AdWords Remarketing. This information is gathered via both first and third-party cookies, including the Google Analytics and Doubleclick Cookies. 

## What Information Do We Share With Third Parties?

_Information Shared with Our Services Providers, Merchants, and Schools._ We may engage third party service providers to work with us to administer and provide the Website and to process and fulfill your purchases or other transactions on the Website. These third-party services providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf. Similarly, if you choose to purchase any deals offered by merchants on our Website, we may provide your name and/or other identifying information (but will not provide your credit card information) to those merchants, and may also provide that information in our reports to the fundraising organizations that benefit from your purchase.

_Information Shared with Other Third Parties._ We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes. We may also share your information (including PII) with third parties to the extent, if any, that you request or affirmatively consent to that sharing. If you submit any information to our Website as a representative of a school or other fundraising organization, we may identify you on our Website as a representative of that organization, but will typically do so only by first name. We may also display your first name in connection with any editorial information or other content you submit for posting to the Website.

_Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions._ Information that we collect from our users, including PII, is a considered to be a business asset. This means if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy or if we are acquired as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your PII may be disclosed or transferred to the third-party acquirer in connection with the transaction.

_Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others._ It is our policy to protect you from having your privacy violated through abuse of the legal systems, whether by individuals, entities or government, and to contest claims that we believe to be invalid under applicable. However, it is also our policy to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties. Accordingly, we reserve the right to disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary: (i) to satisfy or comply with any law, regulation or legal process or to respond to lawful requests, including subpoenas, warrants or court orders; (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the rights, property and safety of third parties or the public in general; and (iv) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

## The Security of Your Information

We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification), and we may make those disclosures to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we’re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access.

## Modifying Your Information

You can access and modify the PII associated with your Schoola account by logging into your account and editing your personal profile. If you want us to delete your PII and your account, please contact us at [help@schoola.com](mailto:help@schoola.com) with your request. We’ll take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. 

## Our Policy Toward Children

Our Website is not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We may modify and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of such changes by posting them on the Website or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll indicate when such changes will become effective. 

## Questions?

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [help@schoola.com](mailto:help@schoola.com) or by mail at:  
Schoola, Inc.  
601 Montgomery Street, Suite 675  
San Francisco, CA 94111
